in previous tutorials i've demonstrated
在前面的教程中，我已经演示了
how to create simple line style drawings
如何创建简单的线条样式图
from photos by using some of the tool
通过使用一些工具从照片中
settings in the pen tool but inkscape
钢笔工具中的设置，但Inkscape
has come a very long way since then and
从那时起已经走过了很长的路，
there's now a better way to do this
现在有一种更好的方法来做这件事
using the power stroke path effect in
在中使用增强笔划路径效果
this lesson i'll be showing you how
这一课我将向你展示如何
[Music]
[音乐]
so let's go over how you can use this
所以让我们来看看如何使用它
handy feature in inkscape we're going to
Inkscape中的便捷功能，我们将
start off by drawing a single line using
首先，使用以下工具绘制一条线
the bezier pen which is located over
位于上面的贝塞尔笔
here in your toolbar or you could access
在您的工具栏中，或者您可以访问
it by pressing the letter b on your
通过在您的计算机上按字母b
keyboard
键盘
i'm going to click on the canvas once to
我要在画布上点击一次，
create a point and then i'm going to
创建一个点，然后我将
hold ctrl on the keyboard and move the
按住键盘上的Ctrl键并移动
line straight across my screen like that
像这样划过我的屏幕
and then click again to create another
然后再次单击以创建另一个
point and then i can let go of control
然后我就可以放手了
and then i'm going to close the path by
然后我要关闭这条小路
pressing enter on the keyboard and now
按键盘上的Enter键，现在
we have a single line here as you can
我们这里只有一行，就像你能做到的
see
看见
now what i'm going to do is grab the
现在我要做的是抓住
edit paths by nodes tool which is
按节点编辑路径工具，该工具是
located over here and i'm going to click
位于这里，我要点击
and drag on this line like this just to
像这样拖着这条线就是为了
give it a little bit of a curve and then
给它一点曲线，然后
i'm going to click on these nodes over
我将点击这些节点
here
这里
and i'm going to get access to these
我要拿到这些
handles and use these handles to make
句柄，并使用这些句柄来制作
this
这
line dip down over here and then rise up
线在这里下降，然后上升
over here so we have a fluid curved line
在这里，我们有一条流体曲线
like that now i'm creating this because
就像现在我创造这个是因为
this is a good
这是一个很好的
uh way to depict what this path effect
呃，用这种方式来描述这条路径的影响
does
会吗？
so once we've done that let's grab the
所以，一旦我们完成了这一点，让我们抓住
selection tool we now have our line
选择工具我们现在有了我们的产品线
selected i'm going to open up the path
我要打开这条路
effects menu by going to path and
通过转到路径和效果菜单
selecting path effects
选择路径效果
and with this line selected i want to
选择了这行后，我想
click this little plus icon down here in
点击下面的小加号图标
the bottom right corner to add a new
在右下角添加一个新的
path effect
路径效应
and the path effect that we're going to
以及我们将要实现的路径效应
be adding from this list is called power
从这个列表中添加的被称为功率
stroke now instead of trying to navigate
立即进行笔划，而不是尝试导航
through this list and find it you can
浏览这份清单，找到它，你可以
just use the search bar up here and type
只需使用此处的搜索栏并键入
in power
掌权
and it should come up right over there
它应该就在那里
as you can see power stroke click on
正如您可以看到的那样，请点击
that
那
and now we have a power stroke applied
现在我们有了一个动力冲程
what we want to do to edit this power
我们想要做什么来编辑这种力量
stroke is come back over here to the
中风在这里又回来了
edit paths by nodes tool
按节点编辑路径工具
and you'll notice on your path you
你会发现在你的人生道路上
should see three pink nodes let me zoom
应该看到三个粉色的节点，让我放大
in a little bit i'm going to hold ctrl
稍后我将按住Ctrl键
and roll up the mouse wheel so you can
卷起鼠标滚轮，这样你就可以
see it better
看得更清楚些
there's one pink node right here in the
有一个粉红色的节点就在这里
center point of the path
路径的中心点
and then over here there's another pink
然后在这里有另一个粉色
point on the
上的点
on the left hand side of the path or
在小路的左侧或
otherwise known as the start point of
也称为的起点
the path where you originally drew the
您最初绘制的路径
path first and then over here towards
先走这条路，然后走到这里
the end point there's another pink path
终点在另一条粉色小路上
now all all of these handles allow you
现在，所有这些手柄都可以让您
to change the width of your stroke
更改笔触的宽度
so if i click and drag on this pink path
所以如果我在这条粉色路径上点击并拖动
right here you can see the stroke is
就在这里，你可以看到笔划是
becoming wider as i move it like this
当我像这样移动它时，它变得更宽
and if i use this handle down here i can
如果我在下面用这个把手，我就能
make this end of the line wider as well
把这条线的这一端也弄宽一点
i could even move this the opposite way
我甚至可以反其道而行之
and get like a little bit of a crossover
然后变得有点跨界
effect there but i'm going to use this
效果，但我要用这个
to make this about that size and then
把这个做得差不多大小，然后
i'll do the same thing over here i'll
我会在这里做同样的事情，我会
make this about that size and another
把这个做成那个大小的，再做一个
thing that you can do is you can move
你能做的就是你可以移动
the location of these handles
这些手柄的位置
so that you can change the width of any
这样您就可以更改任何
particular spot of your line as you see
如你所见，你的线条上的特定位置
me doing here i could give this a line a
我在这里做的我可以给这句话一句
bulge over here so that this kind of
在这里鼓起，这样这种
looks like a leaf or a paintbrush maybe
可能看起来像树叶或画笔
or i could bring this down here so that
或者我可以把这个拿下来，这样
we end up with a
我们最终得到了一个
maybe it looks more like a follicle of
也许它看起来更像一个毛囊
hair or something like that okay so let
头发或类似的东西，好的，让我们
me put this back over here let me show
我把这个放回这里，让我看看
you what some of these tool settings are
您了解其中一些工具设置是什么
over here
在这里
in the bottom right hand corner of the
控件的右下角
screen now if you notice there's a start
现在屏幕如果您注意到有一个开始
cap and then there's an end cap the
盖子，然后还有一个末端盖子
start cap is the beginning of the path
起始封口是路径的起点
that you originally drew and the end cap
你最初画的和端盖
is the end of the path that was
是这条小路的尽头
most recently finished
最近完成的
now if i change this by default it's set
现在，如果我在默认情况下更改此设置，它将被设置
to zero width if i want to change the
如果我想要更改
start cap to rounded
起始封口为四舍五入
or to let's say for example but
或者比方说，但是
it ends up with the flat
它最终成了公寓
edge like that so you could take this
像这样的边缘，这样你就可以拿着这个
handle and bring this over here like
把这个拿过来，就像这样
this and pull this all the way out so
然后把这一切都拉出来
you get this sort of effect right here
你就会在这里得到这种效果
where it kind of looks like a wispy hair
它看起来有点像一缕头发
okay so let me undo that and then
好的，让我解开它，然后
there's other settings in here you could
这里还有其他设置，您可以
try as well you can make this peak
尽你最大的努力，你会达到顶峰的
which ends up with something like this
结果是这样的
right here
就在这里
or you can make this round so that you
或者你可以让这个回合，这样你就可以
have a rounded path like that
有一条像那样的圆形小路
you can make this square so you have a
你可以做这个正方形，这样你就有了一个
squared path and then zero width takes
平方路径，然后采用零宽度
you back to the starting point with the
你回到起点，带着
fine tip like that
像这样的小费很高
so let's put this tool into context and
所以让我们把这个工具放在上下文中，
use it to create a simple abstract
用它来创建一个简单的摘要
mountain range logo i'm going to grab
我要去抢山脉标志
the bezier pen
贝塞尔钢笔
and i'm going to create some points on
我将在以下几个方面提出一些观点
my canvas in the shape of a mountain top
我的山顶形状的画布
with a couple of peaks
有几个山峰
as you can see here like this
如您所见，这里是这样的
and i'll press enter
然后我将按Enter键
and now i'm going to add the power
现在我要添加一种力量
stroke path effect as we did previously
笔划路径效果，就像我们之前做的那样
grab the edit pads by nodes tool i'm
按结点抓取编辑板工具我是
going to use my pink handles over here
我要在这里用我的粉色手柄
to make this a little wider i'm going to
为了让这个问题更广泛一些，我要
use this handle over here and put this
用这里的把手，把这个
towards the top of the base of the leg
朝向腿部底部的顶端
so that it looks a little more
所以它看起来更像是
consistent
始终如一
there we go and i want this side to be a
好了，我希望这一方成为一名
little thicker than the rest of it so
比它的其他部分厚一点，所以
i'll make that a little bigger like that
我会把它做得像那样大一点
now if you notice here the corners of
现在，如果你注意到这里的角落
this mountain range are rounded
这条山脉是圆形的
the reason why that happens is because
发生这种情况的原因是因为
the default setting over here in the
此处的默认设置是
tool settings where it says join
显示为连接的工具设置
is rounded by default if you want
如果需要，默认情况下为四舍五入
corners there what i would recommend
在那里的角落，我会推荐什么
doing is selecting miter and as you can
所做的就是选择斜接，并尽可能地
see now we get sharp corners like that
看，现在我们得到了像那样的尖角
or if you're working with curved paths
或者如果您使用的是曲线路径
sometimes you'll want to use
有时你会想要使用
extrapolated arc as well if the corners
外推圆弧，如果角点
don't show up using miter
不要使用斜接出现
for this demonstration we'll be sticking
对于本演示，我们将坚持
with miter
使用斜接
okay so now that that's done i'm going
好的，现在做完了，我要走了
to create another line i'm going to come
为了创造另一条线路，我要来
over here
在这里
i'm going to draw a line over here
我要在这里划一条线
start a point right there
从那里开始一个点
start another point right there
从那里开始另一个点
and press enter on the keyboard and i'm
然后按下键盘上的Enter键，我就
going to grab the edit pads by nodes
要按节点抓取编辑板
tool i'm just going to click and drag
工具我只需点击并拖动
this down like that
这件事就像那样
and i'll take this and i'll maybe bring
我会拿着这个，也许我会带上
this line up like that
这条线是这样排的
maybe bring this one down a little more
也许把这件再降一点。
we want a nice fluid curve here
我们想要一条流畅的曲线
and i'm going to update my mountain
我要更新我的山
range
量程
to to accommodate this swoosh a little
为了适应这一点
bit i'm going to take this side right
比特，我要站在这一边
here move that up a little bit
这里，把它往上移一点
that's a little better
那好一点了
and now i'm going to apply a power
现在我要施加一种力量
stroke to this line right here
笔划到这里的这条线
use my nodes right here to make this
就在这里使用我的节点来制作这个
wider
更宽
make this a little wider
把这个弄宽一点
and then make this a little wider
然后再加宽一点
and maybe even make this a little wider
甚至可能把它做得更宽一点
okay that's looking a lot better
好的，看起来好多了。
and i'm just going to adjust this a
我要把这个调整成
little bit make sure this is looking
稍微确认一下这个看起来
the way i'd like it to look
我希望它看起来是这样的
and there we go i'd say that's good
我们走吧，我想说这很好
enough so what i'm going to do now is
够了，所以我现在要做的是
grab the selection tool as you can see
如您所见，抓起选择工具
now as you can see here we have created
现在，如您所见，我们已经创建了
a very simple abstract mountain logo now
现在是一个非常简单的抽象的山标志
at any point you can go back and edit
您可以随时返回并编辑
the nodes of these tools you can go back
这些工具的节点可以回溯到
and edit the width of these lines over
并编辑这些线条的宽度
here like that of the power stroke
就像这里的力量冲刺一样
and if at any point you want to finalize
如果你想在任何时候敲定
this so that it becomes an editable path
这将使其成为可编辑路径
all you have to do is select everything
您所要做的就是选择所有内容
and go to path
并转到路径
object to path and if you go back to
对象设置为路径，如果您返回到
your nodes tool now you can see that
您的节点工具现在您可以看到
this is an individual path that was
这是一条曾经的个人道路
created using that power stroke function
使用该电动冲程功能创建
so i think that should do it for today's
所以我认为今天的比赛应该就是这样了
tutorial that is how you can use the
教程，这就是如何使用
power stroke path effect in inkscape
Inkscape中的力量笔划路径效果
before i end this video if you found
在我结束这段视频之前，如果你找到
this lesson useful then consider
这一课很有用，然后考虑
checking out my inkscape master class
查看我的Inkscape大师课
it's a collection of over 60 videos
这是60多个视频的集合
where i go over all of the tools and
在那里我检查了所有的工具和
features in inkscape and i explain what
Inkscape中的功能，我将向您解释
they are and demonstrate how they work
它们是并演示了它们的工作方式
kind of like how i did in this video we
有点像我在这段视频中所做的
even have a private community where you
甚至有一个私人社区，在那里你可以
can ask questions and get help from me
可以问我问题并得到我的帮助
anytime you want and best of all there's
任何你想要的时间，最好的是有
no monthly membership fees you just pay
你只需支付月费就可以了
17 one time and you're in for life i'll
17一次，你会被判终身监禁，我会
have some information about that in the
中有一些关于这方面的信息
description of the video if you want to
视频描述(如果您想要
check that out as always thanks for
一如既往地查看，谢谢
watching
观看
you
你